(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)The problem appears to be unsolvable.
Maybe we could run
some computer simulations.
There are many variables.
It would take forever.
We've gotta be missing something.
Okay. Let's start again.
The movie is playing here at 7:20,
here at 7:40...
...here at 8: 10, and here at 8:45.
(Penny:)All right.
These theaters have to be eliminated.
Why? They're state of the art:
digital projection, surround sound.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but they have no Icee machines.
(Sheldon:)Despite my aggressive
letter-writing campaign, I might add.
(Raj:)What about the multiplex here?
The seats are terrific.
(Sheldon:)They have Twizzlers instead of Red Vines.
No lumbar support can compensate for that.
It's gonna take an hour to eat and I don't
see a Sheldon-approved restaurant...
(Leonard:)...proximate
to a Sheldon-approved theater.
- We could eat after the movie.
- Unacceptable.
(Sheldon:)The delay would result in tomorrow
morning's bowel movement at work.
(Raj:)Hang on, hang on.
There's a 7-Eleven here.